Mike North: 冲浪一个，你想在松散模式下编译你的项目。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Surf one, you want to
compile your project in loose mode.
你首先要确保你的测试通过。
And you begin by making
sure your tests pass.
然后，重命名你所有的文件或一大块你的文件从
And then, rename all your files or
a chunk of your files from
支持任何隐式类型。
JavaScript to TypeScript,
allowing for implicit any types.
每当打字稿编译器无法弹出时，就会弹出隐式 anys
Implicit anys pop up whenever
the TypeScript compiler cannot
推断出更具体和有用的类型。
infer a more specific and useful type.
函数参数就是一个很好的例子。
Good example of this would
be a function argument.
所以打字稿的推断方式只有一个方向。
So the way TypeScript infers things
is kinda only in one direction.
只有通过接收某种值,
It's, only through receiving
a value of some sort,
就像传承下去一样。
and like passing that on.
所以，在这里强调一下这个例子。
So, just to highlight this example here.
迈克 · 诺斯: 这是一个隐式的任何，即使在这里，如果我试图把它分成
&gt;&gt; Mike North: This is an implicit any and
even if down here, if I try to split it to
试图给出线索，它可能是一个字符串，它仍然是一个隐式的任何。
try to give the clue that it might be a
string, it still remains an implicit any.
因为类型信息没有,
Because type information does not,
推论并不是从用法点到论点。
the inference does not flow up from
the point of usage to the argument.
有些语言可以做到这一点，但是这种语言不行。
Some languages do that, this one does not.
所以函数论点被放在
So functional arguments are placed
where you're almost always gonna
得到一个隐含的任何。
get an implicit any.
唯一的情况是，你不会是如果它是一个回电，有一个具体的
The only case where you wouldn't is if
it's a call back, and there's a specific
输入那个回电，记住，我们不需要指定任何东西。
type for that call back, and remember,
we don't have to specify anything there.
这样做的目的是修复导致打字稿编译错误的任何问题。
Your goal in this pass is to fix anything
that is causing TypeScript compile errors.
这种情况经常出现的例子是 JavaScript 类。
Examples of where this will pop up
all the time is JavaScript classes.
当你改用打字稿的时候，你必须去
When you change to TypeScript,
you're gonna have to go and
说明字段及其类型，所以
state the fields and their types, so
你事先就知道什么是有效的领域，什么不是。
you know ahead of time what's
a valid field and what's not.
所以你要解决这种问题,
So you're gonna fix that kind of thing,
非常小心地避免改变任何行为，这是一个拉请求。
being very careful to avoid changing any
behavior, and that is one pull request.
确保您的测试再次通过，并将其合并到。
Make sure your tests have passed again,
and merge that in.